A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.30 (A2004) FA482
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2004.065: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1992-2003; AC.2004.065; 13.1 Cubic Feet 10 standard record storage boxes, R3675-R3684.; 10 standard record storage boxes, R3675-R3684.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.065.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 98001 #647 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - RICE WAXY GENE, 1990-2002 (Box R3684)
    - RF 98001 #650 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - OSMOTIC ADJUSTMENT TO TROPICAL JAPONICA THROUGH MARKER-AIDED SELECTION, 1998-2001 (Box R3684)
    - RF 98001 #661 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES - DISTRIBUTING AND IMPORTING AGRICULTURAL TECHNOLOGY, 1998-2003 (Box R3684)
    - RF 98001 #681 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PUNJAB - PEST RESISTANCE, 1990-2001 (Box R3684)
    - RF 98001 #681 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PUNJAB - PEST RESISTANCE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1990-2001 (Box R3684)
- AC.2004.067: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2004; AC.2004.067; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3686-R3687.; 2 standard record storage boxes, R3686-R3687.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.067.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 98008 #138 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - MAIZE-LEGUME IMPROVEMENT WITH ROCK PHOSTATE SOLUBILIZING, 1999-2000 (Box R3686)
    - RF 98011 #36 - WINROCK INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT - AFRICAN MOSAIC VIRUS AND RESISTANT/TOLERANT CASSAVA, 1998-2001 (Box R3686)
    - RF 98011 #38 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - MOLECULAR MAP OF CASSAVA, 1991-2001 (Box R3686)
    - RF 98012 - BIOSAFETY AND INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS, 1995-1998 (Box R3686)
    - RF 98013 #159 - PORTUGUESE FAMILY PLANNING ASSOCIATION (PORTUGAL) - POLICY DIALOGUE, 1997-2001 (Box R3686)
    - RF 98013 #160 - PRINCETON UNIVERSITY - BIRTH INTERVALS IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1998-2001 (Box R3686)
    - RF 98013 #167 - UNIVERSITY RESEARCH CORP. (BANGLADESH) - UNMET NEED FOLLOW-UP STUDY, 1998-2004 (Box R3686)
    - RF 98013 #175 - POPULATION COUNCIL - GENDER AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH IN INDIA AND PAKISTAN, 1998-2001 (Box R3686)
    - RF 98013 #187 - 2050 - EDUCATE JAPANESE ON REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH ISSUES, 1998-2000 (Box R3686)
    - RF 98014 #26 - UNIVERSITY OF OUAGADOUGOU (BURKINA FASO) - FAMILY PLANNING SERVICES, 1994-2000 (Box R3686)
    - RF 98017 #203 - MUSEUM OF PHOTOGRAPHIC ARTS - EXHIBITION, "THE MODEL WIFE", 1997-2002 (Box R3686)
    - RF 98017 #211 - SOUTHWEST MUSEUM - EXHIBITION, "COMMON THREADS: NAVAJO AND PUEBLO TEXTILES", 1998-2002 (Box R3686)
    - RF 98017 #221 - CALIFORNIA INDIAN BASKETWEAVERS ASSOCIATION - WESTERN REGIONAL INDIGENOUS BASKETWEAVERS GATHERING, 1998-2000 (Box R3686)
    - RF 98019 #13 - COMMUNITY PARTNERS - EFFECTS OF WELFARE IMPLEMENTATION ON THE POOR IN LOS ANGELES; INFORM L.A. HUMAN SERVICES NETWORK OF FINDINGS, 1998-2000 (Box R3687)
    - RF 98020 #26 - AMERICAN SOCIETY FOR TRAINING AND DEVELOPMENT - TEMPORARY STAFFING AND LOWER SKILLED WORKERS CAREER PROSPECTS, 1998-2004 (Box R3687)
    - RF 98020 #28 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS (BOSTON) - MEASUREMENT OF UNEMPLOYMENT AND RELATED LABOR FORCE INDICATORS IN SELECTED COUNTRIES, 1998-2000 (Box R3687)
    - RF 98020 #33 - NEW SCHOOL UNIVERSITY - TRENDS IN U.S. WAGE COLLAPSE, 1998-2002 (Box R3687)
    - RF 98022 #100 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA (CHAPEL HILL) - COMER SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM, 1996-2000 (Box R3687)
    - RF 98022 #104 - PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY - EDUCATION (BOARD OF) - COMER SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM REGIONAL TRAINING CENTER, 1994-1999 (Box R3687)
    - RF 98022 #104 - PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY - EDUCATION (BOARD OF) - COMER SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM REGIONAL TRAINING CENTER - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-1999 (Box R3687)
- AC.2004.069: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2003; AC.2004.069; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3685, R3688.; 2 standard record storage boxes, R3685, R3688.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.069.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 98007ÿ#38 - KIGGUNDU, ANDREW - BANANA WEEVIL WITHIN EAST AFRICAN HIGHLAND BANANAS IN UGANDA, 1998-2002 (Box R3685)
    - RF 98001 #687 - UNIVERSITY OF DELHI (INDIA) - IMPROVED SUBMERGENCE TOLERANCE OF RICE, 1994-2000 (Box R3685)
    - RF 98001 #688 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY (THAILAND) - PLANT-PATHOGEN INTERACTIONS BETWEEN RICE AND RICE BLAST PATHOGEN, 1998-2000 (Box R3685)
    - RF 98002 #524 - INTERNATIONAL FORUM FOR SOCIAL SCIENCES IN HEALTH (VENEZUELA) - SEMINAR ON SOCIAL DETERMINANTS OF HEALTH, 1997-2001 (Box R3685)
    - RF 98005 #177 - ZIMBABWE - AGRICULTURE (MINISTRY OF) - EVALUATION AND DEVELOPMENT OF SOIL FERTILITY TECHNOLOGIES IN CHIHOTA AREA, 1999-2001 (Box R3685)
    - RF 98006 #32 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (DAVIS) - SCREEN FOR STRIGA RESISTANCE IN MAIZE, 1996-2001 (Box R3685)
    - RF 98007 #45 - NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH ORGANIZATION (UGANDA) - NUTRIENT DEMAND/CYCLING IN BANANA-BASED CROPPING SYSTEMS, 1996-2001 (Box R3685)
    - RF 98008 #117 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FINGER MILLET PRODUCTIVITY AND IMPROVEMENT OF SOIL NUTRITION AND WEED MANAGEMENT, 1997-2001 (Box R3685)
    - RF 98008 #123 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - INTEGRATED PEST MANAGEMENT FOR COWPEAS IN UGANDA, 1993-2001 (Box R3685)
    - RF 98008 #132 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - INTEGRATED MANAGEMENT OF PESTS OF COMMON BEANS, 1995-2001 (Box R3685)
    - RF 98023 #14 - AFRICAN MEDICAL AND RESEARCH FOUNDATION (KENYA) - HEALTH SECTOR REFORM SERVICES IN KENYA, 1998-2003 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #17 - (INITIATIVE FOR EQUITY IN HEALTH) - GLOBAL COOPERATION FOR ALLEVIATION OF MICRONUTRIENT MALNUTRITION, 1999-2000 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #18 - (INITIATIVE FOR EQUITY IN HEALTH} - COMMUNICATIONS FOR SOCIAL CHANGE IN TOBACCO CONTROL MEETING, 1999-2000 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #18 - (INITIATIVE FOR EQUITY IN HEALTH} - COMMUNICATIONS FOR SOCIAL CHANGE IN TOBACCO CONTROL MEETING - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1999-2000 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #19 - (INITIATIVE FOR EQUITY IN HEALTH} - NORTH AND SOUTH TOBACCO CONTROL PARTNERSHIP CONFERENCE, 1999-2001 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #2 - NEW ENGLAND MEDICAL CENTER HOSPITALS, INC. - WORKSHOP ON SOCIETY AND HEALTH, 1998-2003 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #27 - AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION - 11TH WORLD CONFERENCE ON TOBACCO OR HEALTH, 1999-2001 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #29 - UNIVERSITI SAINS MALAYSIA - SEMINAR TO REVIEW CHAPTERS OF A BOOK ON HEALTH EQUITY, 1999-2002 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #3 - HASTINGS CENTER - MEDICINE AND THE MARKET, 1997-1999 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #31 - UNIVERSITY OF MELBOURNE (AUSTRALIA) - CONFERENCE ON "EQUITY ORIENTED STRATEGIES FOR HEALTH CARE IN VIETNAM", 1999-2000 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #34 - ARGENTINE SOCIETY FOR EQUITY IN HEALTH (ARGENTINA) - SUPPORT PARTICIPANTS AT MEETING ON INEQUITY AND HEALTH, 1999-2000 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #37 - MYANMAR - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - DISEASE SURVEILLANCE NETWORK, 1999-2003 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #39 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - GLOBAL IMPACT OF TOBACCO ON HEALTH, 1999-2000 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #40 - GIFTS OF HEALTH (ENGLAND) - MEETING ON TRADITIONAL ANTl-MALARIALS, 1999-2000 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #42 - (INITIATIVES FOR EQUITY IN HEALTH) - MEETING TO REVIEW THE STATE OF THE ART IN TB SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY, 1999-2000 (Box R3688)
    - RF 98023 #43 - AFRICAN MEDICAL AND RESEARCH FOUNDATION (KENYA) - MEETING ON HARNESSING INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY FOR COMMUNITY HEALTH, 1999-2002 (Box R3688)
- AC.2004.071: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1998-2004; AC.2004.071; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3689.; 1 standard record storage box, R3689.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.071.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 98025 #16 - APPLIED RESEARCH CENTER - COLORLINES MAGAZINE, 1998-2004 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98025 #8 - CULTURAL ENVIRONMENT MOVEMENT - TELEVISION AND VIEWER CONCEPTION OF REALITY, 1996-2002 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98027 #347 - CENTER FOR THE ARTS AT YERBA BUENA GARDENS - PERFORMANCE WORK, "A SLIGHT VARIANCE", 1998-2000 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98027 #352 - DIVERSEWORKS ARTSPACE - "FUCKING A", A FUTURISTIC RETELLING OF THE SCARLET LETTER, 1998-2001 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98027 #364 - LA PENA CULTURAL CENTER - "THE ALAMEDA PROJECT", 1998-2000 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98027 #380 - AXIS DANCE CO. - DANCE PIECE EXAMINING GENDER, AGE AND PREJUDICE IN CONTEXT OF THE DISABLED, 1999-2001 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #295 - CABREROS SUD, VEENA - "HUSH", 1999-2002 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #296 - CAMPBELL, JIM - INTERACTIVE INSTALLATIONS, "COLOR WORKS", 1999-2002 (Box R3689)
      - RF 98028 #296 - CAMPBELL, JIM - INTERACTIVE INSTALLATIONS, "COLOR WORKS" - DIGITAL, 1999; 2004.071.001; Digital (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #297 - DUBOWSKI, SANDI - DOCUMENTARY, "TREMBLING BEFORE G-D", 1999-2004 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #298 - JEREMIJENKO, NATALIE - "MARKET RESEARCH", EXPERIMENTAL VISUAL ESSAY, 1999-2002 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #299 - JONES, ART - INTERACTIVE CD-ROM PROJECT, 1999-2002 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #300 - LERNER, JESSE - DOCUMENTARY ON AMERICAN ROLE IN YUCATAN PENINSULA, 1999-2002 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #301 - LOYER, ERIK - INTERACTIVE WEB NARRATIVE, "CHROMA", 1999-2000 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #302 - MUSKA, SUSAN - DOCUMENTARY, "WOMEN AND GENOCIDE", 1999-2002 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #303 - RIKER, DAVID H. - NARRATIVE FILM, "BORDER LIVES", 1999-2002 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #304 - ROSENBLATT, JAY - EXPERIMENTAL DOCUMENTARY, "KING OF THE JEWS", 1999-2000 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #305 - SACHS, IRA - "FORTY SHADES OF BLUE", 1999-2002 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #306 - TAJIRI, REA - COMIC MUSICAL, "THE FAMILY BODY", 1999-2004 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #307 - DE LARA RANGEL, MARIA DEL CARMEN - VIDEOS, "GENERO E IDENTIDADES SEXUALES (GENDER AND SEXUAL IDENTITIES)", 1999-2002 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #308 - GRUNER, SILVIA - MOVING IMAGE INSTALLATION, "MATERIA ES DE MATER (MATTER COMES FROM MATER)", 1999-2002 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #309 - MARTINEZ SUAREZ, CARLOS - "SACRED LAND IN A CONFLICT ZONE", 1999-2000 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #312 - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF LA RAZA - LATINO MEDIA CONFERENCE, 1999-2000 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #314 - SEATTLE ART MUSEUM - MEDIA PROGRAM, "I-NET/OPEN STUDIO", 1998-2003 (Box R3689)
    - RF 98028 #315 - OREGON PUBLIC BROADCASTING - 12TH INTERNATIONAL ELECTRONIC CINEMA FESTIVAL, 1998-2002 (Box R3689)
- AC.2004.073: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1978-2004; AC.2004.073; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3690-R3692.; 3 standard record storage boxes, R3690-R3692.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.073.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - RF 98028 #316 - ELECTRONIC ARTS INTERMIX - DOCUMENTARY, "TELEVISION'S FIRST DIGITAL REVOLUTION", 1998-2002 (Box R3690)
      - RF 98028 #316 - NAM JUNE PAIK DVD-ROM, 1998-2002; 2004.073.001; Digital (Box R3690)
    - RF 98028 #31 - 8 HARVESTWORKS - ARTISTS' DATA BANK PROJECT, 1998-2001 (Box R3690)
    - RF 98028 #31 - 9 KCTS TELEVISION - "JOYSTICK NATION" AND WEBSITE, 1999-2000 (Box R3690)
      Cancelled
    - RF 98029 #39 - CENTER FOR BUDGET AND POLICY PRIORITIES - PUBLIC JOB CREATION STRATEGIES; PUBLIC HOUSING WELFARE REFORM, 1999-2001 (Box R3690)
    - RF 98030 #10 - SHOREBANK ADVISORY SERVICES, INC, - ATTRACT BUSINESS INVESTMENT TO INNER-CITY NEIGHBORHOOD MARKETS, 1998-2004 (Box R3690)
    - RF 98030 #9 - NEW SCHOOL UNIVERSITY - TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE PROJECT, 1999-2002 (Box R3690)
    - RF 98031 #48 - EWING MARION KAUFFMAN FOUNDATION - FIRST THINGS FIRST DISTRICT-WIDE SCHOOL REFORM INITIATIVE, 1997-2000 (Box R3690)
    - RF 98031 #53 - SAN DIEGO CITY SCHOOLS - BUILDING AN INFRASTRUCTURE FOR PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT, 1994-2002 (Box R3690)
    - RF 98031 #53 - SAN DIEGO CITY SCHOOLS - BUILDING AN INFRASTRUCTURE FOR PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT, 1994-2002 (Box R3690)
    - RF 98041 #73 - PENNSYLVANIA STATE UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE: AGAINST ALL ODDS: AFRICAN LANGUAGES AND LITERATURES INTO 21ST CENTURY, 1998-2001 (Box R3691)
    - RF 98037 #45 - NATIONAL KOREAN AMERICAN SERVICE AND EDUCATION CONSORTIUM - ASIAN PACIFIC AMERICAN CURRICULUM PACKET, 1998-2002 (Box R3691)
    - RF 98037 #47 - PUBLIC ADVOCATES - COMMUNITY-BASED CIVIC AND HEALTH EDUCATION PROGRAM, 1998-2002 (Box R3691)
    - RF 98037 #50 - CENTER FOR DOCUMENTARY STUDIES, INC. - TRAIN LATINO YOUTHS TO DOCUMENT THEIR EXPERIENCES OF CROSSING BORDERS, 1998-2001 (Box R3691)
    - RF 98037 #52 - SOUTH OF MARKET FOUNDATION - STRATEGIES TO CONFRONT GENTRIFICATION PRESSURES IN SAN FRANCISCO'S SOUTH OF THE MARKET, 1998-2002 (Box R3691)
    - RF 98038 #65 - AL-WASITI ART CENTRE (ISRAEL) - DOCUMENTATION OF PALESTINIAN ART, 1996-2001 (Box R3691)
    - RF 98038 #70 - ASHTAR FOR THEATRE PRODUCTION AND TRAINING (ISRAEL) - "ABU SHAKER'S AFFAIRS '99" AND "WOMEN OF SAND AND MYRRH", 1995-2000 (Box R3691)
    - RF 98038 #71 - UNIVERSITY OF OKLAHOMA - CONFERENCE ON PALESTINIAN REFUGEES, 1999-2000 (Box R3691)
    - RF 98039 #14 - TRINITY COLLEGE - CONFERENCE ON RELIGIOUS PERSECUTION AND US POLICY, 1999-2000 (Box R3691)
    - RF 98041 #75 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - 1999 AFRICAN FILM FESTIVAL, 1998-2000 (Box R3691)
    - RF 98041 #79 - LINKFEST (ZIMBABWE) - NAMIBIA-LINKFEST '99 ARTS FESTIVAL, 1998-2002 (Box R3691)
    - RF 98044 - MEXICAN AMERICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND (MALDEF) - EQUAL EMPLOYMENT OPPORTUNITY, 1978-2003; 5 folders. (Box R3692, Box R3691)
    - RF 98044 - MEXICAN AMERICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND (MALDEF) - EQUAL EMPLOYMENT OPPORTUNITY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1978-2003 (Box R3692, Box R3691)
- AC.2004.075: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2005; AC.2004.075; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3693-R3694.; 2 standard record storage boxes, R3693-R3694.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.075.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 99001 #705 - BAISAKH, NIRANJAN - DISSERTATION FELLOWSHIP IN RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1997-2000 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98048 #12 - SCIENTIFIC & INDUSTRIAL RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT CENTRE (ZIMBABWE) - TRAINING IN BIOSAFETY PROTOCOLS AT WORKSHOP, "BIOSAFETY 2", 1999-2000 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98048 #13 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR THE ACQUISITION OF AGRl-BIOTECH APPLICATIONS - FREEDOM-TO-OPERATE REVIEW FOR PROVITAMIN-A RICE (GOLDEN RICE), 1999-2000 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98048 #2 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR THE ACQUISITION OF AGRl-BIOTECH APPLICATIONS - BUILDING INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY MANAGEMENT CAPACITY IN ASIA, 1999-2000 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98048 #4 - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY - IMPACT OF TRANSGENIC COTTON ON FARMERS IN CHINA, 1999-2002 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98048 #8 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR FOOD AND AGRICULTURAL POLICY - REPORT ON RISKS AND BENEFITS OF AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1999-2001 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98048 #9 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - WORKSHOP ON PLANT VARIETY PROTECTION PATENT SYSTEM, 1999-2000 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98052 #161 - UNIVERSITY OF DURBAN-WESTVILLE (SOUTH AFRICA) - STUDENTS' CHANCES TO OBTAIN A UNIVERSITY EDUCATION, 1999 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98052 #164 - (FEMALE PARTICIPATION IN AFRICAN EDUCATION) - BASIC LEARNING COMPETENCIES AND LIFE SKILLS OF GIRLS IN ZIMBABWE, 2000-2002 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98052 #166 - (FEMALE PARTICIPATION IN AFRICAN EDUCATION) - BASIC LEARNING COMPETENCIES AND LIFE SKILLS OF GIRLS IN UGANDA, 2000-2002 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98052 #167 - (FEMALE PARTICIPATION IN AFRICAN EDUCATION) - BASIC LEARNING COMPETENCIES AND LIFE SKILLS OF GIRLS IN KENYA, 2000-2001 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98054 #12 - FORDHAM UNIVERSITY - WORKING GROUP ON THE ARTS AND HUMANITIES, 1997-2005 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98055 #609 - UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS (AUSTIN) - INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON LATIN AMERICAN/LATINO ART, 1999-2000 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98055 #611 - LA MORADA CORP. FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF WOMEN (CHILE) - CONFERENCE, "MEMORY IN LATIN AMERICAN TRANSITIONS", 1999-2001 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98055 #616 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (DAVIS) - RESIDENT FELLOWS (CENTER FOR HEMISPHERIC STUDIES OF INDIGENOUS PEOPLES), 1994-2003 (Box R3693)
    - RF 98055 #625 - UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO - CONFERENCE, "THE FUTURE OF THE QUEER PAST", 1999-2001 (Box R3693)
    - RF 99001 #710 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (DAVIS) - RICE RESISTANCE TO BACTERIAL BLIGHT AND BLAST, 1995-2001 (Box R3693)
    - RF 99001 #719 - PUNJAB AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - SOMATIC CELL, PROTOPLAST AND ANTHER CULTURE OF INDICA RICE, 1990-2004; 2 folders. (Box R3694)
    - RF 99001 #735 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - IMPACT OF DROUGHT ON MODERN FARMING PRACTICES IN EASTERN INDIA AND BANGLADESH, 1998-2000 (Box R3694)
    - RF 99001 #739 - UNIVERSITY OF OTTAWA - ANTHER AND POLLEN-SPECIFIC PROMOTERS, 1991-2002 (Box R3694)
    - RF 99001 #739 - UNIVERSITY OF OTTAWA - ANTHER AND POLLEN-SPECIFIC PROMOTERS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-2002 (Box R3694)
    - RF 99001 #742 - CUU LONG DELTA RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (VIETNAM) - MARKER-ASSISTED SELECTION WORKSHOP, 1999-2001 (Box R3694)
    - RF 99001 #745 - JOHN INNES CENTRE (ENGLAND) - RICE TRANSFORMATION TRAINING AND TECHNOLOGY DEVELOPMENT CENTER, 1994-2003 (Box R3694)
    - RF 99001 #753 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - TRANSFORMATI ON WITH XA21 FOR BLIGHT/BLAST RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1998-2001 (Box R3694)
- AC.2004.079: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1997-2004; AC.2004.079; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3695-R3698.; 3 standard record storage boxes, R3695-R3697.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.079.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 97045 #70 - ACTION RESEARCH TO IMPROVE REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH SERVICE DELIVERY - INTERVENTION RESEARCH WORKSHOP IN INDIA, 1998-2001 (Box R3695)
      - Repro. Health Intervention Research Workshop Key Docs Dsk #1, 2004.079.001; floppy disk
      - Repro. Health Intervention Research Workshop Key Docs Dsk #2, 2004.079.002; floppy disk
      - Ahmedabad Workshop Presentation Documents, 2004.079.003; floppy disk
      - Youth Survey Question Bank, 2004.079.004; floppy disk
      - Chris Elias' Presentation Documents Pt 1, 2004.079.005; floppy disk
      - Report & Other Documents, 2004.079.006; floppy disk
      - Presentations 1/2, 2004.079.007; floppy disk
      - Presentations 2/2, 2004.079.008; floppy disk
    - RF 97045 #70 - ACTION RESEARCH TO IMPROVE REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH SERVICE DELIVERY - INTERVENTION RESEARCH WORKSHOP IN INDIA - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1998-2001; 6 folders. (Box R3695)
    - RF 99001 #776 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - NINTH ANNUAL MEETING OF THE INTERNATIONAL PROGRAM ON RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1999-2001 (Box R3696)
    - RF 99001 #757 - NATIONAL POLYTECHNIC INSTITUTE (MEXICO CITY) - RICE PRODUCTIVITY INCREASE, 1990-2001 (Box R3696)
    - RF 99001 #760 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - RICE CULTIVAR IMPROVEMENT IN THAILAND USING MOLECULAR MARKER-ASSISTED SELECTION, 1999-2001 (Box R3696)
    - RF 99001 #766 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - MOLECULAR CHARACTERIZATION OF COLD TOLERANT RICE GERMPLASM FROM NEPAL, 1999-2000 (Box R3696)
    - RF 99001 #768 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - DROUGHT RESISTANCE PHENOTYPING IN LOWLAND FIELDS OF BANGLADESH, 1999 (Box R3696)
    - RF 99001 #770 - GRIENGGRAI PANTUWAN - DROUGHT RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1994-2002 (Box R3696)
    - RF 99001 #772 - CUU LONG DELTA RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (VIETNAM) - RICE IMPROVEMENT IN THE MEKONG DELTA, 1998-2002 (Box R3696)
    - RF 99001 #777 - INSTITUTE OF MOLECULAR AGROBIOLOGY (SINGAPORE) - BROAD-SPECTRUM DISEASE RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1997-2004 (Box R3696)
    - RF 99001 #779 - CHINA NATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - MEETING ON DROUGHT TOLERANT RICE AND MAIZE, 1999-2000 (Box R3696)
    - RF 99003 #185 - DYCK, ELIZABETH - LEGUME RESEARCH PROJECTS IN KENYA, 1994-2001 (Box R3696)
    - RF 99003 #186 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - REGIONAL WORKSHOP ON SOIL TESTING AND PLANT ANALYSIS, 1999-2000 (Box R3696)
    - RF 99003 #187 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY - ON-FARM EVALUATION, 1988-2002; 3 folders. (Box R3697)
    - RF 99003 #187 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY - ON-FARM EVALUATION - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1988-2002 (Box R3697)
    - RF 99003 #188 - REHABILITATION OF ARID ENVIRONMENTS CHARITABLE TRUSTS (KENYA) - "SUSTAINABLE UTILIZATION OF THE BARINGO DRYLANDS (KENYA) PROJECT", 1999-2001 (Box R3697)
    - RF 99003 #189 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (KENYA) - SOIL FERTILITY AND REPLENISHMENT IN VIHIGA AND SIAYA DISTRICTS, 1996-2004 (Box R3697)
    - RF 99003 #197 - INTERNATIONAL CROPS RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR THE SEMI-ARID TROPICS (INDIA) - SOIL FERTILITY TECHNOLOGIES IN MALAWI, 1997-2000 (Box R3697)
    - RF 99003 #198 - MALAWI - PLANNING SEMINARS; PUBLICATION AND DISTRIBUTION OF ITS POLICY ANALYSIS INITIATIVE, 1998-2002 (Box R3697)
    - RF 99006 #147 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - PRINTING OF CROP SCIENCE DEPARTMENT WORKSHOP PROCEEDINGS, 1998-2002 (Box R3698)
    - RF 99006 #159 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - WEED MANAGEMENT IN THE CHINYIKA AREA, 1996-2002 (Box R3698)
    - RF 99006 #160 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - CROP MANAGEMENT IN THE CHINYIKA AREA, 1996-2002 (Box R3698)
    - RF 99006 #167 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - BACTERIAL PATHOGENS AND ROOT-KNOT NEMATODES OF COW PEA AND PEA CROPS, 1999-2001 (Box R3698)
    - RF 99006 #178 - EDUARDO MONDLANE UNIVERSITY (MOZAMBIQUE) - BIOLOGICAL CONTROL AGENTS AGAINST CEREAL STEMBORERS, 1997-2002 (Box R3698)
    - RF 99006 #185 - EGERTON UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - WHEAT/CHICKPEA ROTATION CROPPING SYSTEM, 1995-2000 (Box R3698)
    - RF 99006 #188 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - FOURTH FORUM REGIONAL MEETING, 2000-2001 (Box R3698)
    - RF 99006 #190 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY - AGROFORESTRY AND INTERCROPPING AND INSECT PESTS, 1997-2002 (Box R3698)
    - RF 99006 #191 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - IMPROVED FODDER TREES BY WOMEN FARMERS IN SMALLHOLDER FARMING, 1997-2002 (Box R3698)
    - RF 99006 #192 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - EFFECT OF INTERCROPPING MAIZE AND BEANS ON MAJOR DISEASES OF BEANS, 1996-2000 (Box R3698)
    - RF 99006 #193 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - SURFACE SOIL AND EROSION-INDUCED NUTRIENT LOSSES IN MAIZE-LEGUME CROPPING, 1997-2002 (Box R3698)
    - RF 99006 #195 - MOI UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - PHOSPHATE ROCK EVALUATION PROJECT, 1998-2002 (Box R3698)
    - RF 99006 #196 - MOI UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - PHOSPHOROUS RESOURCE EXPLORATORY PROJECT FOR WESTERN KENYA, 1996-2002 (Box R3698)
- AC.2004.080: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2004; AC.2004.080; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3699-R3700.; 2 standard record storage boxes, R3699-R3700.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.080.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 99007 #41 - SWISS FEDERAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (SWITZERLAND) - ENGINEERED DISEASE RESISTANCE IN CASSAVA, 1996-2001 (Box R3699)
    - RF 99006 #197 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - VASCULAR PUNCTURE TECHNIQUE AND MAIZE STREAK VIRUS, 1997-2002 (Box R3699)
    - RF 99006 #201 - AFRICA UNIVERSITY (ZIMBABWE) - SOIL MANAGEMENT OPTIONS FOR IMPROVED GROUNDNUT PRODUCTION, 1993-2001 (Box R3699)
    - RF 99007 #43 - UNIVERSITY OF BATH (ENGLAND) - CASSAVA BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR HONGYING LI, 1998-2000 (Box R3699)
    - RF 99007 #47 - SCIENTIFIC & INDUSTRIAL RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT CENTRE (ZIMBABWE) - BIOTECHNOLOGIST: ATTEND CONFERENCE; VISIT COLLABORATING SCIENTISTS, 2000-2001 (Box R3699)
    - RF 99008 #32 - INDEPTH (GHANA) - NETWORK MEETING IN JOHANNESBURG, 2000-2001 (Box R3699)
    - RF 99009 #206 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL ON MANAGEMENT OF POPULATION PROGRAMMES (MALAYSIA) - POLICY DIALOGUE IN ASIA-PACIFIC/COOPERATIVE STRATEGIES, 1999-2001 (Box R3699)